[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":53229,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":174003,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure th at when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":9501,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":183505,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":17198,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":200704,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2566,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":203271,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":6537,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":209808,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2452,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":212260,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the secon d one to  it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":5402,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":217664,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1711,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":219375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5474,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":224849,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1137,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":225986,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":5973,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":231960,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub> 6</sub>  0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1210,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":233170,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3470,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":236640,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":3478,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":240119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br / ><br />  (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":5296,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":245416,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":980,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":246396,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your resu lt.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4347,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":250744,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":943,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":251688,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":4445,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":256134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1175,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":257310,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4153,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":261463,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":893,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":262356,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":16581,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":278938,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own invers e under  +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":24431,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":303370,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":6845,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":310216,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1112,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":311329,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><b r /> (Re member, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3355,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":314684,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":997,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":315682,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2703,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":318386,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2072,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":320459,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2946,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":323405,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<s ub>6</su b>.","rt":1304,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":324709,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":8336,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":333046,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1531,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":334578,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed startin g with t he left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":15249,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":349828,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no w ay to ma ke 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":74160,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":423989,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":39391,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":463381,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":6693,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":470075,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generat or is an  element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":81895,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":551970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":2804,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":554775,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generat or is an  element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":39811,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":594587,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":6128,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":600715,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":[" No"],"rt":5656,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":606371,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":2067,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":608439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operat ion. Aft er that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":17518,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":625957,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":10453,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":636411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1188,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":637599,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":2975,"trial_type":"questio n","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":640575,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":6274,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":646849,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4253,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":651103,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2734,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":653837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3123,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":656961,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":11967,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":668929,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain i n words  how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not applied.","explanation_history":["4+12","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so no further opwere","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so no further opwer","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so no further opwe","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so no further opw","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so no further op","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so no","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so n","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not necessary.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not pe.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not per.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not perf.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not perfo.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not perfor.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not perform. ","4+1=5  which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not performe.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not performed.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not a.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not ap[.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not ap.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not apo.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not ap.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not app.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not appl.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not appli.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not applie.","4+1=5 which is less than 9, so the subtraction is not applied."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":85204,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":754134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"8+4=12 which is greater than 9, so 9 is subtracted from 12 which results in 3 as the answer.","explanation_history":["8+4=12 weh","8+4=12 we","8+4=12 whicxh i","8+4=12 whicxh ","8+4=12 whicxh","8+4=12 whicx","8+4=12 which is greater than 9, so 9 is subtracted fg","8+4=12 which is greater than 9, so 9 is subtracted from 12 which results in 3 as the answee","8+4=12 which is greater than 9, so 9 is subtracted from 12 which results in 3 as the answer./","8+4=12 which is greater than 9, so 9 is subtracted from 12 which results in 3 as the answer."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":51943,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":806078,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"If the +9 operator is applied on any valid number with 0, the result is the same number, so 0 is the identity.","explanation_history":["Any numbn","Any number","Applying the +9 operator wi","Applying the +9 operator w","Applying the +9 operator ","Ap","A","0","IF the","IF","I","f the ","If the +9 opwe","If the +9 opw","If the +9 operator is applied on any number wiuth","If the +9 operator is applied on any number wiut","If the +9 operator is applied on any number wiu","If the +9 operator is applied on any number with 0","If the +9 operator is applied on any vnumber with 0","If the +9 operator is applied on any vainumber with 0","If the +9 operator is applied on any vailnumber with 0","If the +9 operator is applied on any vainumber with 0","If the +9 operator is applied on any vanumber with 0","If the +9 operator is applied on any valnumber with 0","If the +9 operator is applied on any valinumber with 0","If the +9 operator is applied on any valid number w ith 0","If the +9 operator is applied on any valid number with 0, ty","If the +9 operator is applied on any valid number with 0, t","If the +9 operator is applied on any valid number with 0, thje","If the +9 operator is applied on any valid number with 0, thj","If the +9 operator is applied on any valid number with 0, the result is the same number, so 0 is the identityu","If the +9 operator is applied on any valid number with 0, the result is the same number, so 0 is the identity."],"response_history":["0"],"rt":213397,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1019475,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":18958,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1038434,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.12-0 "},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":3328,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1041763,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3687,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1045450,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the ad dition u nder +9 is 0. Since the result is 0, the inverse of 3 is 6.","explanation_history":["3","Under +9, addinfg","Under +9, addinf","Under +9, addin","Under +9, addi","Under +9, add","Under +9, ad","Under +9, a","Under +9, 3","Under +9, 3 +9 6 = 0","Un","U","3+9","3+","3","3+6=9, under","3+6=9,","3+6=9.","3+6=9.  Under +9m, ","3+6=9.  Under +9m,","3+6=9.  Under +9m","3+6=9.  Under +9m,","3+6=9.  Under +9m","3+6=9.  Under +9, the result ius","3+6=9.  Under +9, the result iu","3+6=9.  Under +9, the result is 0 since the sum is ","3+6=9.  Un","3+6=9.  U","3+6=9.  ","3+6=9. ","3+6=9. Followinfg ","3+6=9. Followinfg","3+6=9. Followinf","3+6=9. Following the rtu","3+6=9. Following the rt","3+6=9. Following the rules odf ","3+6=9. Following the rules odf","3+6=9. Following the rules od","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result add","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result ad","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result a","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the  o","3+6= 9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addiction un","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addiction u","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addiction ","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addiction","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addictio","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addicti","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addict","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addic","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is zero","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is zer","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is ze","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is z0","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is z","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 suin","3+6=9. Foll owing th e rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 sui","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 su","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 suin","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 sui","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 su","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 since the zxu","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 since the zx","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 since the z","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 since the sum is 9 or tg","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 since the sum is 9 or t","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 since the sum is 9 or ","3+6=9. Following the rules of + 9, the r esult of the addition under +9 is 0 since the sum is 9 or","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 since the sum is 9 o","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 since the sum is 9 ","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 since the sum is 9","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 since t","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 since ","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 si","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 s","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0 ","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0,","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0.  ==","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is  0.  =","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0.  ","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0. ","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0. Since ther","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0. Since the result is 0, the i ","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0. Since the result is 0, the inverse io","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0. Since the result is 0, the inverse i","3+6=9. Following the rules of +9, the result of the addition under +9 is 0. Since the result is 0, the inverse of 3 is 6."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":218276,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1263726,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"mul ti","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=1\n...and so forth\n\n","explanation_history":["Performinf","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in tyhe","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in tyh","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in ty","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+23","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+2","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of  all digi ts 0-8.\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+2=4\n2+2+2=6\n2+23","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+2=4\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2=8","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+2=4\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2=","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+2=4\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+2=4\n2+2+2","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+2=4\n2+2+","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+2=4\n2+2","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+2=4\n2+","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the  generat ion of all digits 0-8.\n2+2=4\n2","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+2=4\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+2=4","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+2=","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+2","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2+","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n2","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\ne,","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\ne,g,","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\ne,g","Performing successive additions under +9  using 2  results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\ne,","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\ne.g.","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\ne.g","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\ne.","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\ne","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2-","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 \n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 \n"," Performi ng successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (wh\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (whe\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (wher\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where \n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where _\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where \n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where +\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0 -8.\n\n2 +2=4 (where + \n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is \n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)_\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + i s +9)\n2 _\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2_+\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2_\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8 .\n\n2+2 =4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2=6\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+ 2+2=6\n2 +2+2+2=9\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=89\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2=8\n\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2=8\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2=\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the gene ration o f all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=1\n\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=1\n.\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+ 2+2=6\n2 +2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=1\n..\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=1\n...\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=1\n...an\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=1\n...and\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=1\n...and \n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=1\n...and so\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6 \n2+2+2+ 2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=1\n...and so \n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=1\n...and so fo\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=1\n...and so for\n\n","Performing successive additions under +9 using 2 results in the generation of all digits 0-8.\n\n2+2=4 (where + is +9)\n2+2+2=6\n2+2+2+2=8\n2+2+2+2+2=1\n...and so forth\n\n"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":755232,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":2018959,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3  and 6.   1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated.\n\n3+3=6 (where + is +9)\n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","explanation_history":["Successive +9 operatrio","Successive +9 operatri","Successive +9 operatr","Successive +9 operations on 3 onl","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates the ","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates the","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates th","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates t","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3,","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7,","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 asn","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 asn","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 as","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated.\n\n3+3=6\n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 canno t be gen erated.\n\n3+3=6 \n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated.\n\n3+3=6 (\n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated.\n\n3+3=6 (wh\n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated.\n\n3+3=6 (whe\n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated.\n\n3+3=6 (wher\n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated.\n\n3+3=6 (where\n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated.\n\n3+3=6 (where \n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 can not be g enerated.\n\n3+3=6 (where +\n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated.\n\n3+3=6 (where + \n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated.\n\n3+3=6 (where + i\n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated.\n\n3+3=6 (where + is \n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated.\n\n3+3=6 (where + is +\n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated.\n\n3+3=6 (where + is +9\n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6","Successive +9 operations on 3 only generates 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated.\n\n3+3=6 (where + is +9)\n3+3+3=0\n3+3+3+3=3\n3+3+3+3+3=6"],"response_history":["No"],"rt":167450,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":2186410,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Successive +9 operations on 5 generates all valid digits 0-8.\n\n5+5=1 (where + is +9)\n5+5+5=6\n.\n.\n.\n5+5+5+5+5+5+5+5+5+5=5","explanation_history":["Successive +9 operations on 5 generates all digits 0-8.","Successive +9 operations on 5 generates all vdigits 0-8.","Successive +9 operations on 5 generates all valdigits 0-8.","Successive +9 operations on 5 generates all validigits 0-8.","Successive +9 operations on 5 generates all validdigits 0-8.","Successive +9 operations on 5 generates all valid digits 0-8.\n\n","Successive +9 operations on 5 generates all valid digits 0-8.\n","Successive +9 operations on 5 generates  all vali d digits 0-8.\n\n5+5=1 (where + is +9(","Successive +9 operations on 5 generates all valid digits 0-8.\n\n5+5=1 (where + is +9_)","Successive +9 operations on 5 generates all valid digits 0-8.\n\n5+5=1 (where + is +9_","Successive +9 operations on 5 generates all valid digits 0-8.\n\n5+5=1 (where + is +9)_","Successive +9 operations on 5 generates all valid digits 0-8.\n\n5+5=1 (where + is +9)\n5+5+5=6\n./","Successive +9 operations on 5 generates all valid digits 0-8.\n\n5+5=1 (where + is +9)\n5+5+5=6\n.\n.\n.\n5+5+5+5+5+5+5+5+5+5=5"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":266087,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":2452498,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"Successive +9 operations on 6 generates only 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4 ,5,7 and  8 cannot be generated.","explanation_history":["Successice ","Successice","Successic","Successive +9 operations on 6 generates only 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7,8 ","Successive +9 operations on 6 generates only 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7,8","Successive +9 operations on 6 generates only 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7,","Successive +9 operations on 6 generates only 0,3 and 6.  1,2,4,5,7 and 8 cannot be generated."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":130457,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2582956,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":16842,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2599798,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n-1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["n-1","inn-1","invn-1","inven-1","invern-1","inversn-1","inversen-1","inverse n-1","inverse = n-1","inn-1","in-1","n-1"],"rt":52775,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2652574,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"i(x) = n-x","explain":true,"explanation":"When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since the rules state n is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or equal  to n.  S o, i(x)=n-x.","explanation_history":["The inverse of an elem","The inverse of an ele","The inverse of an el","T","When the operator i","When the operator +_n is applied on an eleme","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and itr","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverts","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its invert","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  G","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  The resil","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  The resi","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  The resui","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  The result 0 ","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  The res","When the operator +_n is applied on an elemen t x and  its inverse, the result is 0.  The re","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  The r","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  The re","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  The r","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  The ","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  The","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i=n ","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(=n ","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x=n ","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n  since an y result of","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since any res","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since any re","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since any r","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since any ","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since any","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since an","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since a","When the operator +_n is appli ed on an  element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since any result from an addirtio","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since any result from an addirti","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since any result from an addirt","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since any result from an addir","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since any result from an addition which is greater than or equ","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since a","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.   That r esult comes about when x+i(x)=n since n is subtracted from any sum thaty is ","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since n is subtracted from any sum thaty is","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since n is subtracted from any sum thaty i","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since n is subtracted from any sum thaty ","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since n is subtracted from any sum thaty","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since n is subtracted from any sum that ios","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result  is 0.   That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since n is subtracted from any sum that io","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since n is subtracted from any sum that i","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since n is subtracted from any sum that ","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since n is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or euiq","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since n is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or eui","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since n is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or eu","When the opera tor +_n  is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since n is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or equal to n.  So, i(x)=n-x.","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since tn is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or equal to n.  So, i(x)=n-x.","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since thn is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or equal to n.  So, i(x)=n-x.","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since then is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or equal to n.  So, i(x)=n-x.","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since the n is subtracted from any sum that  is grea ter than or equal to n.  So, i(x)=n-x.","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since the rn is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or equal to n.  So, i(x)=n-x.","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since the run is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or equal to n.  So, i(x)=n-x.","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since the rulen is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or equal to n.  So, i(x)=n-x.","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since the rules n is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or equal to n.  So, i(x)=n-x.","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is  0.  Tha t result comes about when x+i(x)=n since the rules sn is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or equal to n.  So, i(x)=n-x.","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since the rules stn is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or equal to n.  So, i(x)=n-x.","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since the rules statn is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or equal to n.  So, i(x)=n-x.","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since the rules staten is subtracted from any sum that is greater than or equal to n.  So, i(x)=n-x.","When the operator +_n is applied on an element x and its inverse, the result is 0.  That result comes about when x+i(x)=n since the rules state n is subtracted from any sum that is gre ater tha n or equal to n.  So, i(x)=n-x."],"response_history":["inv = n-x","in = n-x","i = n-x","ix = n-x","i = n-x","i( = n-x","i(x = n-x","i(x) = n-x"],"rt":332586,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2985160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is greater than 1, along with multiples of that factor that are less than n are generators.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I think ","1 is always a generator, andf ","1 is always a generator, andf","1 is always a generator, and I think the lower","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is not 1, and its  multip,. e","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is not 1, and its multip,.","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is not 1, and its multip,","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is not ","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n t","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n ","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is greater 1","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is greater 1, along with multiples of that factor that are less than n are generay","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is greater 1, along with multiples of that factor that are less than n are generators.","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is greater t1, along with multiples of that factor that are less than n are generators.","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of  n that  is greater th1, along with multiples of that factor that are less than n are generators.","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is greater thas1, along with multiples of that factor that are less than n are generators.","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is greater thasn1, along with multiples of that factor that are less than n are generators.","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is greater thas1, along with multiples of that factor that are less than n are generators.","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is greater tha1, along with multiples of that factor that are less than n are generators.","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is greater thab1, along with multiples of that factor that are less than n are generators.","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is greater tha1, along with multiples of th at facto r that are less than n are generators.","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is greater than1, along with multiples of that factor that are less than n are generators.","1 is always a generator, and I think the lowest factor of n that is greater than 1, along with multiples of that factor that are less than n are generators."],"rt":560713,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":3545874,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":16134,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":3562008,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator un der +<su b>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":16366,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":3578374,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":52526,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":3630900,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"m ulti","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the lowest divisor > 1, multiples of that divisor, and 0.  The other valid digits under +_n are excluded from the sequence.","explanation_history":["The results","The results of sic","The results of si","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divs","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor a","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor wio","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will always result in 0","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will always result in ","The results of successive +_n operations o n a divi sor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repo","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the f","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the divsort","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the divsor","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the divso","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the divs","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include th e diviso r, multip.e","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the divisor, multip.","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the divisor, multiples of the de","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the d","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the lowest divs","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the lowest divisor (that is ","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results tha t includ e the lowest divisor > 1","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the lowest divisor > 1, multiples of that divisoe","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the lowest divisor > 1, multiples of that divisor,","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the lowest divisor > 1, multiples of that divisor, and 0.  The other valis ","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the lowest divisor > 1, multiples of that divisor, and 0.  The other valis","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence o f result s that include the lowest divisor > 1, multiples of that divisor, and 0.  The other valid digits under +_n are excluded from the dequence.","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the lowest divisor > 1, multiples of that divisor, and 0.  The other valid digits under +_n are excluded from the dequence","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the lowest divisor > 1, multiples of that divisor, and 0.  The other valid digits under +_n are excluded from the d","The results of successive +_n operations on a divisor of n or a multiple of a divisor will generate a repeating sequence of results that include the lowest divisor > 1, multiples of that divisor, and 0.  The other valid digits under +_n are excluded from the sequence."],"response_history":["True"],"rt":387553,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":4018454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always","Sometimes","Always"],"rt":258375,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":4276830,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"The answer is sometimes  because  the case where x=1 results in 2 which cannot be a generator when n is an even number.","explanation_history":["Ther ","Ther","The","Thwe ","Thwe","Thw","The answer is sometimes because the case where x=2","The answer is sometimes because the case where x=1 results in 2 which casnno","The answer is sometimes because the case where x=1 results in 2 which casnn","The answer is sometimes because the case where x=1 results in 2 which casn","The answer is sometimes because the case where x=1 results in 2 which cas","The answer is sometimes because the case where x=1 results in 2 which cannot be  ","The answer is sometimes because the case where x=1 results in 2 which cannot be a generator when n is even","The answer is sometimes because the case where x=1 results in 2 which cannot be a generator when n is eve","The answer is sometimes because the case where x=1 results in 2 which cannot be a generator when n is ev","The answer is sometimes because the case where x=1 results in 2  which ca nnot be a generator when n is e","The answer is sometimes because the case where x=1 results in 2 which cannot be a generator when n is an even number."],"response_history":["Always","Sometimes"],"rt":338277,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":4615109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":26371,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":4641480,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":3192,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":4644673,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"45","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["45"],"rt":3141,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":4647814,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":8575,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":4656390,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the  most adv anced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Some advanced calculus.  I cannot recall the exact course title.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Some high level calculis","Some high level calculi","Some high level calculus.  I cannot recall the exact coiurse","Some high level calculus.  I cannot recall the exact coiurs","Some high level calculus.  I cannot recall the exact coiur","Some high level calculus.  I cannot recall the exact coiu","Some high level calculus.  I cannot recall the exact coi","Some high level calculus.  I cannot recall the exact course title.","Some a calculus.  I cannot recall the exact course title.","Some ad calculus.  I cannot recall the exact course title.","Some adv calculus.  I cannot recall the exact course title.","Some adva calculus.  I c annot re call the exact course title.","Some advan calculus.  I cannot recall the exact course title.","Some advanc calculus.  I cannot recall the exact course title.","Some advance calculus.  I cannot recall the exact course title.","Some advanced calculus.  I cannot recall the exact course title."],"rt":180746,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":4837138,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":16492,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":4853630,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":10140,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":4863770,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":11300,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":4875070,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":9234,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":4884304,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4674,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":4888978,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male"," Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":2260,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":4891238,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Englisdh","Englisd","English"],"rt":7577,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":4898816,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":7462,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":4906278,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":[],"rt":11036,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":4917314,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]